MUHAMMAD AWAIS

FULL STACK ENGINEER

CONTACT

- **4** 03157499811
- Zain Hostel Near Lahore Leads University DHA Phase 5

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind CSS
- Responsive Design
- Java Script
- React Js
- Php
- Laravel
- MySql
- Cpp
- Git & Github
- MS Office

LANGUAGES

- English
- Urdu
- Punjabi



PROFILE

My name is Muhammad Awais. After my second year of studies, I developed a keen interest in coding. I learned frontend development through YouTube tutorials and then completed an internship at Lighthouse Technologies where I focused on React JS. Subsequently, I moved to Lahore and joined Solutionwin Technologies to learn PHP and Laravel. I've been working here as a full-stack engineer for the past year.



WORK EXPERIENCE

extensively used Bootstrap to create many websites.

Lighthouse Technologies

Front-end Developer

I worked at LighthouseTechnologies for 3 months where I learned React and built numerous website and dashboard frontends for them. I

08-2023 to 10-2023

Salaar interprices Lahore

11-2023 to 15-01-2024

Front-end Developer

I interviewed at Salar Enterprises and was selected. I developed a dashboard frontend for them as part of my role. However, I later decided to leave the company.

Solutionwin Technologies

16-01-2024 - till now

Full Stack Developer

At Solutionwin Technologies, I gained expertise in PHP, Laravel, and MySQL. I've been involved in multiple projects, handling tasks such as bug fixing, feature development, and automating data processes using Google Apps Script. This includes creating and importing data into Google Sheets.



EDUCATION

Lahore Leads University

2024 to continue

BSIT

Degree College Sillanwali

2022 to 2023

ICS

Arif Academy Of Science

2022 to 2023

In Science